자연어 쿼리,tagging된 자연어 쿼리,활용 여부,DB Query,,,,
What is the name of band Freddie Mercury played in?,What is the name of band <PERSON> played in?,O,match (n:Human)-[r:PART_OF]-(m:RockBand) where n.name=<PERSON> return m.name,,,,
what is the name of justin bieber brother?,what is the name of <PERSON> brother?,O,match (p:Human)-[r:SIBLING]-(s:Human) where p.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what character did natalie portman play in star wars?,what character did <PERSON> play in <MISC>?,X,작품속 역할 정보 없음,,,,
what state does selena gomez?,what state does <PERSON>?,X,질문 불분명,,,,
what country is the grand bahama island in?,what country is the <LOCATION> in?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(country) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return country.name ,,,,
what kind of money to take to bahamas?,what kind of money to take to <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what character did john noble play in lord of the rings?,what character did <PERSON> play in <MISC>?,X,4와 중복,,,,
who does joakim noah play for?,who does <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where are the nfl redskins from?,where are the <ORGANIZATION> from?,O,match (org)-[:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(loc) where org.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
where did saki live?,where did <PERSON> live?,X,RESIDENCE relation 없음,,,,
how old is sacha baron cohen?,how old is <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.dateOfBirth,,,,
what two countries invaded poland in the beginning of ww2?,what <NUMBER> countries invaded <LOCATION> in the beginning of <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what time zone am i in cleveland ohio?,what time zone am i in <LOCATION>?,O,match (location)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(tz) where location.name=<LOCATION> return tz.name,,,,
who did draco malloy end up marrying?,who did <PERSON> end up marrying?,O,match (m:Human)-[:SPOUSE]-(s:Human) where m.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
which countries border the us?,which countries border the <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
where is rome italy located on a map?,where is <LOCATION> located on a map?,O,match (c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locatorMapImage; match(c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locationMap,,,,
what is nina dobrev nationality?,what is <PERSON> nationality?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what country does iceland belong to?,what country does <LOCATION> belong to?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(country) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return country.name ,,,,
which kennedy died first?,which <PERSON> died <ORDINAL>?,O,"match (m:Human)-[:PART_OF]-(q:RockBand {name:'Queen'}) with m, min(m.dateOfDeath) as mdd  where m.dateOfDeath = mdd return m.name",,,,
what books did beverly cleary write?,what books did <PERSON> write?,O,match (m:Human)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who did the philippines gain independence from?,who did the <LOCATION> gain independence from?,X,역사적 사실 정보 없음,,,,
where to fly into bali?,where to fly into <LOCATION>?,X,<LOCATION>에 가까운 공항,,,,
who is the prime minister of ethiopia?,who is the prime minister of <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what to see near sedona arizona?,what to see near <LOCATION>?,X,POI 정보 없음,,,,
what high school did president bill clinton attend?,what high school did <PERSON> attend?,O,match (h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what form of government does russia have today?,what form of government does <LOCATION> have <DATE>?,O,match (m)-[:BASIC_FORM_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(g) where m.name=<LOCATION> return g.name,,,,
what movies does taylor lautner play in?,what movies does <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what year lebron james came to the nba?,what year <PERSON> came to the <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (h:Human)-[r:MEMBER_OF]-(org) where h.name=<PERSON> return r.Since,,,,
what did the german revolution lead to?,what did the <MISC> lead to?,X,,,,,
how much did adriana lima gain during pregnancy?,how much did <PERSON> gain during pregnancy?,X,,,,,
what does thai mean?,what does <MISC> mean?,O,match (t) where t.name=<MISC> return t.descEn,,,,
which wife did king henry behead?,which wife did king <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
who was ishmael's mom?,who was <PERSON>'s mom?,X,,,,,
what was malcolm x trying to accomplish?,what was <PERSON> trying to accomplish?,X,,,,,
where are the netherlands on a world map?,where are <LOCATION> on a world map?,O,match (c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locatorMapImage; match(c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locationMap,,,,
what is the president of brazil?,what is the president of <LOCATION>?,O,match (m)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where m.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what are the major cities in france?,what are the major cities in <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:COUNTRY]-(location) where location.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what city did esther live in?,what city did <PERSON> live in?,X,RESIDENCE relation 없음,,,,
what sport do the toronto maple leafs play?,what sport do the <ORGANIZATION> play?,X,,,,,
what is saint nicholas known for?,what is <PERSON> known for?,X,,,,,
what is cher's son's name?,what is <PERSON>'s son's name?,O,match (person)-[:CHILD]-(c) where person.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what is martin cooper doing now?,what is <PERSON> doing <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what party was andrew jackson?,what party was <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what is medicare a?,what is <MISC> a?,X,,,,,
what county is the city of hampton va in?,what county is the city of <LOCATION> in?,O,match (city)-[:COUNTRY]-(location) where city.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
what is the name of the first harry potter novel?,what is the name of the <ORDINAL> <PERSON> novel?,X,,,,,
what did william shakespeare do for a living?,what did <PERSON> do for a living?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what county is heathrow airport in?,what county is <LOCATION> in?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
where did dmitri mendeleev study science?,where did <PERSON> study science?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what movie is josh hutcherson in?,what movie is <PERSON> in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what is there to do in laredo tx?,what is there to do in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what season did tony soprano get shot?,what season did <PERSON> get shot?,X,,,,,
where do the san francisco giants play home games?,where do the <ORGANIZATION> play home games?,X,,,,,
what year did william jennings bryan run for president?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> run for president?,X,,,,,
what was the name of frederick douglass book?,what was the name of <PERSON> book?,O,match (h)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where h.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who was queen victoria's parents called?,who was queen <PERSON>'s parents called?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what movies did sally field win an oscar for?,what movies did <PERSON> win an oscar for?,X,,,,,
what is the first book sherlock holmes appeared in?,what is the <ORDINAL> book <PERSON> appeared in?,O,match (h)-[:PRESENT_IN_WORK]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what type of car does michael weston drive?,what type of car does <PERSON> drive?,X,,,,,
where does lena river begin and end?,where does <PERSON> begin and end?,X,,,,,
what countries do people speak portuguese?,what countries do people speak <MISC>?,O,match (c)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(lang) where lang.name=<MISC> return c.name,,,,
where to exchange euros in pittsburgh?,where to exchange euros in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what are the names of walt disney kids?,what are the names of <PERSON> kids?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(c) where p.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
who is in the band bush?,who is in the band <MISC>?,O,match (p)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where b.name=<MISC> return p.name,,,,
what was tupac name in juice?,what was <MISC> name in juice?,X,,,,,
what timezone is australia gmt?,what timezone is <LOCATION> gmt?,O,match (location)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(tz) where location.name=<LOCATION> return tz.name,,,,
who does maggie grace play in taken?,who does <PERSON> play in taken?,X,,,,,
what style of music did louis armstrong play?,what style of music did <PERSON> play?,O,match (p)-[:GENRE]-(g) where p.name=<PERSON> return g.name,,,,
when is summer in australia sydney?,when is <DATE> in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what tv show did joey lawrence play on?,what tv show did <PERSON> play on?,X,,,,,
what timezone is denver co?,what timezone is <LOCATION> ?,O,match (location)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(tz) where location.name=<LOCATION> return tz.name,,,,
what character did brian austin green play on 90210?,what character did <PERSON> play on <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
where does jackie french live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
what form of government was practiced in sparta?,what form of government was practiced in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
when did the colorado rockies go to the world series?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> go to the world series?,X,,,,,
who was peter parker's first girlfriend?,who was <PERSON>'s <ORDINAL> girlfriend?,O,match (h)-[:PARTNER]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what college did matt lauer attend?,what college did <PERSON> attend?,O,match (h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where to go in london england?,where to go in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what school did joan miro attend?,what school did <PERSON> attend?,O,match (h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where did france colonise?,where did <LOCATION> colonise?,X,,,,,
who was vincent van gogh inspired by?,who was <PERSON> inspired by?,O,match (h)-[:INFLUENCED_BY]-(w) where h.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where to get married in jacksonville nc?,where to get married in <LOCATION> ?,X,,,,,
what time zone am i in michigan?,what time zone am i in <LOCATION>?,O,match (location)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(tz) where location.name=<LOCATION> return tz.name,,,,
when did the new york knicks win a championship?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> win a championship?,X,,,,,
what is the official language of china 2010?,what is the official language of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what was woodrow wilson's major accomplishments?,what was <PERSON>'s major accomplishments?,X,,,,,
where is jack daniels factory?,where is <PERSON> factory?,X,,,,,
what language do the speak in pakistan?,what language do the speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
where is santa clara university?,where is <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
which part of korea is communist?,which part of <LOCATION> is communist?,X,,,,,
where did timothy mcveigh go to prison?,where did <PERSON> go to prison?,X,,,,,
what sea does the yangtze river flow into?,what sea does the <LOCATION> flow into?,X,,,,,
who miley cyrus engaged to?,who <PERSON> engaged to?,X,,,,,
what is charles darwin famous for?,what is <PERSON> famous for?,O,match (h)->[:COMPOSER]-(w) where h.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who founded the roanoke settlement?,who founded the <LOCATION> settlement?,O,match (o)->[:FOUNDED_BY]-(h) where o.name=<LOCATION> return o.name,,,,
what kind of money should i take to jamaica?,what kind of money should i take to <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
who is robert downey jr wife?,who is <PERSON> wife?,O,match (m:Human)-[:SPOUSE]-(s:Human) where m.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where do the ny rangers play?,where do the <ORGANIZATION> play?,X,,,,,
where is jefferson davis buried?,where is <PERSON> buried?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_BURIAL]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
who does the author stephenie meyer play in the movie twilight?,who does the author <PERSON> play in the movie <MOVIE>?,X,,,,,
when will oscar pistorius compete?,when <PERSON> compete?,X,,,,,
what years have the dallas cowboys won the superbowl?,what <DURATION> have the <ORGANIZATION> won the <MISC>?,X,,,,,
what awards has louis sachar won?,what awards has <PERSON> won?,O,match (h)-[:AWARD_RECEIVED]-(a) where h.name=<PERSON> return a.name,,,,
who are the current senators from missouri?,who are the <DATE> senators from <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who was the president after jfk died?,who was the president after <PERSON> died?,X,,,,,
what is the best currency to take to egypt 2013?,what is the best currency to take to <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what are the countries in the united kingdom?,what are the countries in the <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:CONTAINS_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(t) where c.name=<LOCATION> return t.name,,,,
what planes does the navy have?,what planes does the <ORGANIZATION> have?,X,,,,,
where did benjamin franklin died?,where did <PERSON> died?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
where to visit in n. ireland?,where to visit in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what to do in cancun with family?,what to do in <LOCATION> with family?,X,,,,,
what is the local language of israel?,what is the local language of <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what city and state was the air force academy established?,what city and state was the <ORGANIZATION> established?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(n) where m.name=<ORGANIZATION> return n.name,,,,
what's the national sport of puerto rico?,what's the national sport of <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what religion are people in russia?,what religion are people in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what did shawnee smith play in?,what did <PERSON> play in?,X,,,,,
what countries did queen victoria reign over?,what countries did queen <PERSON> reign over?,X,,,,,
where did dr seuss go to school?,where did dr <PERSON> go to school?,X,,,,,
what team does luis suarez play for?,what team does <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what are dollars called in spain?,what are dollars called in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
who plays meg in family guy?,who plays <PERSON> in family guy?,X,,,,,
what high school did tim allen go to?,what high school did <PERSON> go to?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what is the world's tallest building in dubai called?,what is the world's tallest building in <LOCATION> called?,X,,,,,
where does asiana airlines fly to?,where does <ORGANIZATION> fly to?,X,,,,,
what movie did angelina jolie direct?,what movie did <PERSON> direct?,X,,,,,
where did martin luther king got shot?,where did <PERSON> got shot?,X,,,,,
where to visit near bangkok?,where to visit near <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who does christina milian have a baby by?,who does <PERSON> have a baby by?,X,,,,,
what year did tut became king?,what year did <PERSON> became king?,X,,,,,
who is the current president of the dominican republic in 2010?,who is the current president of the <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
who has been married to julia roberts?,who has been married to <PERSON>?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where do baltimore ravens play?,where do <ORGANIZATION> play?,X,,,,,
where does the un get its funding?,where does the <ORGANIZATION> get its funding?,X,,,,,
who does brandon dubinsky play for?,who does <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
who all has dated taylor swift?,who all has dated <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:PARTNER]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what is the dominant language in israel?,what is the dominant language in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what are the main languages of nigeria?,what are the main languages of <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what jobs did ben franklin do?,what jobs did <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what bible does the catholic church follow?,what bible does the <MISC> church follow?,X,,,,,
who plays lola bunny in the looney tunes show?,who plays <PERSON> in the looney tunes show?,X,,,,,
what stadium did the chicago cardinals play in?,what stadium did the <ORGANIZATION> play in?,X,,,,,
who did rufus wainwright married?,who did <PERSON> married?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where did c.s. lewis go to college?,where did <PERSON> go to college?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what did nick clegg study at university?,what did <PERSON> study at university?,X,,,,,
who is the president of the european union 2011?,who is the president of the <ORGANIZATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what school did cassie bernall go to?,what school did <PERSON> go to?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what movie did james frey write?,what movie did <PERSON> write?,X,,,,,
what did rob kardashian get surgery for?,what did <PERSON> get surgery for?,X,,,,,
what did st. matthew do?,what did <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
when does harry potter come out on dvd deathly hallows 2?,when does <PERSON> come out on dvd deathly hallows <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what was nelson mandela's religion?,what was <PERSON>'s religion?,O,match (h)-[:RELIGION]-(r) where h.name=<PERSON> return r.name,,,,
who will win the 2011 nhl stanley cup?,who will win the <DATE> <ORGANIZATION> stanley cup?,X,,,,,
what is henry clay known for?,what is <PERSON> known for?,O,MATCH p=(p)-[r:COMPOSER]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,?,,,
who did axl rose marry?,who did <ORGANIZATION> rose marry?,X,,,,,
what years did brett favre go to the super bowl?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> go to the super bowl?,X,,,,,
what is the money of spain called?,what is the money of <LOCATION> called?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
where are sunbeam microwaves made?,where are <ORGANIZATION> microwaves made?,X,,,,,
who was elected president of the philippines?,who was elected president of the <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what cities does ryanair fly to?,what cities does <ORGANIZATION> fly to?,X,,,,,
what time zone is oklahoma state?,what time zone is <LOCATION> state?,O,match (loc)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(tz) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return tz.name,,,,
who was the apostle paul considered to be?,who was the apostle <PERSON> considered to be?,X,,,,,
what currency does ontario canada use?,what currency does <LOCATION> use?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what instrument does justin bieber?,what instrument does <PERSON>?,O,match (h)->[:INSTRUMENT]-(i) where h.name=<PERSON> return i.name,,,,
what team did shaq play for first?,what team did <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where was kennedy when he got shot?,where was <PERSON> when he got shot?,X,,,,,
who do derek fisher play for?,who do <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where did the casey anthony case take place?,where did the <PERSON> case take place?,X,,,,,
where did pres clinton go to college?,where did <PERSON> go to college?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what was the name of the original seattle baseball team?,what was the name of the original <LOCATION> baseball team?,X,,,,,
who was general cornwallis american revolution?,who was general <PERSON> american revolution?,X,,,,,
what type of monarchy did england have?,what type of monarchy did <LOCATION> have?,X,,,,,
when were the texas rangers started?,when were the <ORGANIZATION> started?,O,match (o) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return o.inception,,,,
where did the houston oilers football team go?,where did the <ORGANIZATION> football team go?,X,,,,,
what do they call football in spanish?,what do they call football in <MISC>?,X,,,,,
where did pauley perrette go to college?,where did <PERSON> go to college?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where does niles crane live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
where was gabriel faure born?,where was <PERSON> born?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
who is the governor of kentucky 2012?,who is the governor of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
who is the senator of the united states 2010?,who is the senator of the <LOCATION> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where did the massive allied invasion of northern france take place in june 1944?,where did the massive allied invasion of northern <LOCATION> take place in <DATE>?,X,,,,,
which countries are part of the united kingdom?,which countries are part of the <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CONTAINS_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(part) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return part.name,,,,
what is the postcode for london?,what is the postcode for <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who killed vincent chin dvd?,who killed <PERSON> dvd?,X,,,,,
what other books did jules verne wrote?,what other books did <PERSON> wrote?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what is the currency name of brazil?,what is the currency name of <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what language does fiji?,what language does <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what is the second percy jackson book called?,what is the <ORDINAL> <PERSON> book called?,X,,,,,
what did gregor mendel conducted his experiments on?,what did <PERSON> conducted his experiments on?,X,,,,,
who did jon gosselin cheat with?,who did <PERSON> cheat with?,X,,,,,
where is mitsubishi headquarters?,where is <ORGANIZATION> headquarters?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
where is jay cutler now?,where is <PERSON> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what influenced vincent van gogh work?,what influenced <PERSON> work?,O,match (h)-[:INFLUENCED_BY]-(influencer) where h.name=<PERSON> return influencer.name,,,,
what time zones are there in the us?,what time zones are there in the <LOCATION>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what are the 5 biggest cities in the usa?,what are the <NUMBER> biggest cities in the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what language do australian people speak?,what language do <MISC> people speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
who did ben stiller play in megamind?,who did <PERSON> play in <MOVIE>?,X,,,,,
what countries did queen victoria rule?,what countries did queen <PERSON> rule?,O,match (s)-[:HEAD_OF_STATE]-(p) where p.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who are betty white's parents?,who are <PERSON>'s parents?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(c) where c.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
where did jeff dunham go to school?,where did <PERSON> go to school?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what college did kevjumba?,what college did <PERSON>?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who does david james play for 2011?,who does <PERSON> play for <DATE>?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what was the purpose of the 1964 gulf of tonkin resolution?,what was the purpose of the <DATE> gulf of <LOCATION> resolution?,X,,,,,
what movies did diana ross play in?,what movies did <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what is the zip code for minneapolis?,what is the zip code for <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what country is the west bank located in?,what country is the <LOCATION> located in?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
who won golden boot?,who won <MISC>?,O,match (h)-[:AWARD_RECEIVED]-(a) where a.name=<MISC> return h.name,,,,
where did jane mansfield die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
where is the thames river located?,where is the <LOCATION> located?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
when did kings last win stanley cup?,when did kings last win <MISC>?,X,,,,,
what school did william shakespeare attend?,what school did <PERSON> attend?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what money do they use in chile?,what money do they use in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what college did peyton manning?,what college did <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what are the 2 conferences in the nfl?,what are the <NUMBER> conferences in the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
when did jennifer lopez start on in living color?,when did <PERSON> start on in living color?,X,,,,,
when is portland marathon?,when is <LOCATION> marathon?,X,,,,,
what character does ellen play in finding nemo?,what character does <PERSON> play in finding nemo?,X,,,,,
when was the last time the ny giants were in the super bowl?,when was the last time the <ORGANIZATION> were in the super bowl?,X,,,,,
what are all the names of harry potter?,what are all the names of <MISC>?,X,,,,,
what does nick cannon play in?,what does <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what sort of government does brazil have?,what sort of government does <LOCATION> have?,X,,,,,
which airport is best to fly into milan?,which airport is best to fly into <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where did matthias schleiden go to school?,where did <PERSON> go to school?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what county is rihanna from?,what county is <PERSON> from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what happened to daddy yankee?,what happened to <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
what country is located in the balkan peninsula?,what country is located in the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what 6 states border south dakota?,what <NUMBER> states border <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what are the main languages spoken in spain?,what are the main languages spoken in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what songs did mozart write?,what songs did <PERSON> write?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what language do they speak in thai?,what language do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
who is the new senator of montana?,who is the new senator of <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
which airport to fly in rome?,which airport to fly in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where are the ruins of pompeii?,where are the ruins of <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what language people speak in afghanistan?,what language people speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what language do people speak in brazil wikipedia?,what language do people speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what cities should i visit in california?,what cities should i visit in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where was princess leia raised?,where was princess <PERSON> raised?,X,,,,,
what is the name of the pittsburgh steelers head coach?,what is the name of the <ORGANIZATION> head coach?,X,,,,,
when does canada's wonderland close?,when does <LOCATION>'s wonderland close?,X,,,,,
when did the lakers win the championship?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> win the championship?,X,,,,,
what year was the great san francisco fire?,what <DURATION> was the great <LOCATION> fire?,X,,,,,
what countries share borders with france?,what countries share borders with <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what did patrick swayze sing?,what did <PERSON> sing?,O,match (s)-[:PERFORMER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what style of art is salvador dali?,what style of art is <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:GENRE]-(g) where h.name=<PERSON> return g.name,,,,
what city was leonardo da vinci from?,what city was <PERSON> from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what did george v die of?,what did <PERSON> die of?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what are the three major rivers in south america?,what are the <NUMBER> major rivers in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what other discoveries did isaac newton discover?,what other discoveries did <PERSON> discover?,X,,,,,
who started pixar?,who started <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (o)-[:FOUNDED_BYU]-(h) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.name,,,,
who is tia and tamera mowry parents?,who is <PERSON> parents?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(c) where c.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what political party was lincoln?,what political party was <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what would have happened if germany had won ww1?,what would have happened if <LOCATION> had won ww1?,X,,,,,
what kind of government is china?,what kind of government is <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where is the nation of greece located?,where is the nation of <LOCATION> located?,O,match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what three countries does mexico border?,what <NUMBER> countries does <LOCATION> border?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what year was the new york blackout?,what <DURATION> was the <LOCATION> blackout?,X,,,,,
which countries have english as native language?,which countries have <MISC> as native language?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what position does rafael furcal play?,what position does <PERSON> play?,X,,,,,
what are major exports of the usa?,what are major exports of the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what shows did kellie martin star in?,what shows did <PERSON> star in?,O,match (s)-[:PERFORMER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where did rihanna grow up?,where did <PERSON> grow up?,X,,,,,
where is whistler mountain located?,where is <LOCATION> mountain located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
what currency do i need in cuba?,what currency do i need in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) return currency.name,,,,
who is julia roberts married to 2012?,who is <PERSON> married to?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what sport does rebecca adlington compete in?,what sport does <PERSON> compete in?,X,,,,,
when did the christchurch quake happened?,when did the <LOCATION> quake happened?,X,,,,,
what other countries does canada trade with?,what other countries does <LOCATION> trade with?,X,,,,,
what to see in singapore at night?,what to see in <LOCATION> at <TIME>?,X,,,,,
who played mason capwell?,who played <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what is james madison most famous for?,what is <PERSON> most famous for?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who did the maccabees revolted against?,who did the <ORGANIZATION> revolted against?,X,,,,,
where was the battle of antietam creek?,where was the battle of <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
during what war did abraham lincoln serve as president?,during what war did <PERSON> serve as president?,X,,,,,
who are shakespeare's parents names?,who are <PERSON>'s parents names?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(c) where c.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
where is she from shakira?,where is <PERSON> from ?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
who plays captain kirk in 2009?,who plays captain <PERSON> in <DATE>?,X,,,,,
who did hera marry?,who did <PERSON> marry?,O,match (h)-[:SPOUSE]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what type of guitar does kirk hammett play?,what type of guitar does <PERSON> play?,X,,,,,
what language they speak in the philippines?,what language they speak in the <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
where is the kakadu national park located?,where is the <LOCATION> national park located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
what to do with kids in denver today?,what to do with kids in <LOCATION> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what money does jamaica use?,what money does <LOCATION> use?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what year did william mckinley became president?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> became president?,X,,,,,
what date did kennedy become president?,what date did <PERSON> become president?,X,,,,,
what timezone is colorado in right now?,what timezone is <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
who owns aston martin 2012?,who owns <ORGANIZATION> <DATE>?,O,match (o)-[:OWNED_BY]-(h) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.name,,,,
what disease has jack osbourne got?,what disease has <PERSON> got?,X,,,,,
what do the islamic believe?,what do the <MISC> believe?,O,match (h)-[:RELIGION]-(r) where h.name=<MISC> return r.name,,,,
who will david beckham play for in 2013?,who will <PERSON> play for in <DATE>?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what language they speak in taiwan?,what language they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
who owns the toronto maple leafs?,who owns the <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (o)-[:OWNED_BY]-(h) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.name,,,,
what county is novato california in?,what county is <LOCATION> in?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what are the basic beliefs of sikhism?,what are the basic beliefs of <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where did hernando cortez die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
who was liz taylor married too?,who was <PERSON> married too?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where was the ancient region of mesopotamia?,where was the ancient region of <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
who was real housewives brandi married to?,who was real housewives <PERSON> married to?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
when did the charlotte bobcats first play in the nba?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> <ORDINAL> play in the nba?,X,,,,,
what's the book hitler wrote in prison?,what's the book <PERSON> wrote in prison?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where is the ottoman empire located?,where is the <MISC> empire located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
which city held the summer olympics twice?,which city held the <DATE> <MISC> twice?,X,,,,,
who are the green bay packers owned by?,who are the <ORGANIZATION> owned by?,O,match (o)-[:OWNED_BY]-(h) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.name,,,,
what inspired langston hughes to write poetry?,what inspired <PERSON> to write poetry?,O,match (h)-[:INFLUENCED_BY]-(w) where h.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what languages are there in switzerland?,what languages are there in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
when was the last time the orioles had a winning season?,when was the last time the <ORGANIZATION> had a winning season?,X,,,,,
what does australia export?,what does <LOCATION> export?,X,,,,,
where did henry knox die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
who was the queen of the iceni tribe?,who was the queen of the <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:HEAD_OF_STATE]-(h) where c.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what is the name of the first prophet of islam?,what is the name of the <ORDINAL> prophet of <MISC>?,X,,,,,
who is married to garry trudeau?,who is married to <PERSON>?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where does norway get their oil?,where does <LOCATION> get their oil?,X,,,,,
what language do they speak in northern ireland?,what language do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) return lang.name,,,,
what countries make up continental europe?,what countries make up continental <LOCATION>?,O,match (c:Country)-[:CONTINENT]-(e) where e.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what do abrahamic religions have in common?,what do <MISC> religions have in common?,X,,,,,
what did johnny crawford sing?,what did <PERSON> sing?,O,match (s)-[:PERFORMER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what did abraham lincoln do before he was president?,what did <PERSON> do before he was president?,X,,,,,
what sport does sally pearson compete in?,what sport does <PERSON> compete in?,X,,,,,
where is atlanta texas located?,where is <LOCATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
who did elton john marry first?,who did <PERSON> marry <ORDINAL>?,O,match (h)-[:SPOUSE]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where is tom cruise from?,where is <PERSON> from?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what movies did madonna appear in?,what movies did <PERSON> appear in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
where does leland chapman live now?,where does <PERSON> live <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where was the roman colosseum located?,where was the <MISC> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
what date was abraham lincoln inaugurated?,what date was <PERSON> inaugurated?,X,,,,,
what invention did henry ford invent?,what invention did <PERSON> invent?,X,,,,,
what time zone is new york under?,what time zone is <LOCATION> under?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
when did mayans predict end of the world?,when did <MISC> predict end of the world?,X,,,,,
what is the name of the book hitler wrote while in prison?,what is the name of the book <PERSON> wrote while in prison?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who voiced meg in the pilot?,who voiced <PERSON> in the pilot?,X,,,,,
what albert einstein do for math?,what <PERSON> do for math?,X,,,,,
where did bashar al assad study?,where did <PERSON> study?,X,,,,,
who plays lois lane in superman returns?,who plays <PERSON> in superman returns?,X,,,,,
what did joseph lister do for science?,what did <PERSON> do for science?,X,,,,,
who uses new king james bible?,who uses new king <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what films did charlie chaplin direct?,what films did <PERSON> direct?,X,,,,,
who does lea michele dating in real life?,who does <PERSON> dating in real life?,X,,,,,
when did joe walsh leave the eagles?,when did <PERSON> leave <MISC>?,X,,,,,
when was the musical annie written?,when was the musical <PERSON> written?,X,,,,,
what should you see in london?,what should you see in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who does billy beane work for now?,who does <PERSON> work for <DATE>?,X,member_of_sports_team,,,,
what subatomic particles did jj thomson discover?,what subatomic particles did <PERSON> discover?,X,,,,,
what films have taylor lautner been in?,what films have <PERSON> been in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
who were anakin skywalker's parents?,who were <PERSON>'s parents?,O,match (p)-[:CHILD]-(c) where c.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what country is the name natalie from?,what country is the name <PERSON> from?,X,natalie 이름이 유래된 나라,,,,
who played the voice of aladdin?,who played the voice of <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what exactly did dale earnhardt die from?,what exactly did <PERSON> die from?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what year did miami heat win the championship?,what <DURATION> did <ORGANIZATION> win the championship?,X,,,,,
what kind of government did benito mussolini have?,what kind of government did <PERSON> have?,X,,,,,
who was emperor diocletian?,who was emperor <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
who is chelsea kane?,who is <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
who is darwin and what is his theory?,who is <PERSON> and what is his theory?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what did obama study in school?,what did <PERSON> study in school?,X,,,,,
where did deion sanders play baseball?,where did <PERSON> play baseball?,X,member_of_sports_team,,,,
who is the new governor of oregon?,who is the new governor of <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what continent is south africa part of?,what continent is <LOCATION> part of?,O,match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
who was michael jackson's best friend?,who was <PERSON>'s best friend?,X,,,,,
what movies has taylor lautner been in 2011?,what movies has <PERSON> been in <DATE>?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
where does the australian prime minister reside?,where does the <MISC> prime minister reside?,X,,,,,
what did kate winslet get an oscar for?,what did <PERSON> get an oscar for?,X,,,,,
what company did henry ford work for?,what company did <PERSON> work for?,X,,,,,
what happened to thomas cromwell's children?,what happened to <PERSON>'s children?,X,,,,,
where indian ocean is located?,where <LOCATION> is located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
what year was the navy chief established?,what <DURATION> was the <ORGANIZATION> chief established?,X,,,,,
what year did the orioles win 100 games?,what <DURATION> did the <ORGANIZATION> win <NUMBER> games?,X,,,,,
who was mary's mother?,who was <PERSON>'s mother?,O,match (h)-[:MOTHER]-(m) where h.name=<PERSON> return m.name,,,,
where is american express located?,where is <ORGANIZATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
what is the china money called?,what is the <LOCATION> money called?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what is the government of spain today?,what is the government of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where is the howard university located?,where is the <ORGANIZATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
where did terrell owens get traded to?,where did <PERSON> get traded to?,X,,,,,
what do catholics call their god?,what do <MISC> call their god?,X,,,,,
what is the capital of alaska state?,what is the capital of <LOCATION> state?,O,match (cap)-[:CAPITAL_OF]-(n) where n.name=<LOCATION> return cap.name,,,,
what was the soviet union?,what was the <LOCATION>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what college did jeff corwin go to?,what college did <PERSON> go to?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who speaks farsi?,who speaks <MISC>?,O,match (h)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(lang) where lang.name=<MISC> return h.name,,,,
who was neptune discovered by?,who was <LOCATION> discovered by?,X,,,,,
who were the major trade partners of russia?,who were the major trade partners of <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what did corey haim really die of?,what did <PERSON> really die of?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where did pavlova originate?,where did <MISC> originate?,O,match (m)-[:COUNTRY_OF_ORIGIN]-(c) where m.name=<MISC> return c.name,,,,
where did nathaniel hawthorne die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where did jack johnson go to high school?,where did <PERSON> go to high school?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who played maxie jones on general hospital?,who played <PERSON> on general hospital?,X,,,,,
what military school did poe attend?,what military school did <PERSON> attend?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what are buddhist gods?,what are <ORGANIZATION> gods?,X,,,,,
who influenced wolfgang amadeus mozart?,who influenced <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:INFLUENCED_BY]-(w) where h.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
when was the last dallas cowboys super bowl win?,when was the last <ORGANIZATION> super bowl win?,X,,,,,
what language do they speak in iceland wikipedia?,what language do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
when was blessed kateri born?,when was blessed <PERSON> born?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
when did the bali bombings occur?,when did the <LOCATION> bombings occur?,X,,,,,
what is the political system in south africa?,what is the political system in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what is the currency in croatia 2012?,what is the currency in <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
where did joe montana go to high school?,where did <PERSON> go to high school?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what cases does the supreme court have original jurisdiction over?,what cases does the <ORGANIZATION> have original jurisdiction over?,X,,,,,
where is the nation of palestine?,where is the nation of <LOCATION>?,O,match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what are the greek titans?,what are the <MISC> ?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what countries speak english primarily?,what countries speak <MISC> primarily?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where lang.name=<MISC> return h.name,,,,
what states does the missouri river touch?,what states does the <LOCATION> touch?,O,match (s)-[:LOCATED_IN_OR_NEXT_TO_BODY_OF_WATER]-(loc) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return s.name,,,,
what is in liverpool england?,what is in <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(loc) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return o.name,,,,
what state is harvard college located?,what state is <ORGANIZATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
where was leonardo da vinci when he died?,where was <PERSON> when he died?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what money do japanese use?,what money do <MISC> use?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what is the time zone in oklahoma city?,what is the time zone in <LOCATION>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what killed whitney houston?,what killed <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what kind of government did the mali empire have?,what kind of government did the <LOCATION> empire have?,X,,,,,
what is the religion of israel people?,what is the religion of <LOCATION> people?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what is mount st helens?,what is <LOCATION>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what airport is closest to sandals grande in st lucia?,what airport is closest to sandals grande in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
which country is north of the usa?,which country is north of the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where does drew gordon play?,where does drew <PERSON> play?,X,,,,,
who was the first russian president?,who was the <ORDINAL> <LOCATION> president?,X,,,,,
what language does people in netherlands speak?,what language does people in <LOCATION> speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what type of language does china speak?,what type of language does <LOCATION> speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) wher h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what countries around the world speak french?,what countries around the world speak <MISC>?,O,match (h)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(lang) where lang.name=<MISC> return h.name,,,,
who is esther hicks?,who is <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what does michael vick do?,what does <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
in which province is johannesburg?,in which province is <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(p) where o.name=<LOCATION> return p.name,,,,
where was john lennon standing when he was shot?,where was <PERSON> standing when he was shot?,X,,,,,
what time do atlantic city bars close?,what time do <LOCATION> bars close?,X,,,,,
what state did al gore represent?,what state did <PERSON> represent?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
who voiced darth vader in revenge of the sith?,who voiced <PERSON> in <MOVIE>?,X,,,,,
what type of art is henri matisse famous for?,what type of art is <PERSON> famous for?,O,match (h)-[:GENRE]-(g) where h.name=<PERSON> return g.name,,,,
what to do in laughlin nevada?,what to do in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who plays princess padme in star wars?,who plays princess <PERSON> in <MOVIE>?,X,,,,,
where to ski in andorra reviews?,where to ski in <LOCATION> reviews?,X,,,,,
who was louis riel?,who was <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
who was judy garland married to?,who was <PERSON> married to?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where is abraham lincoln hometown?,where is <PERSON> hometown?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
what disease did helen keller?,what disease did <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:MEDICAL_CONDITION]-(d) where h.name=<PERSON> return d.name,,,,
what is the name of money in brazil?,what is the name of money in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what year did lakers win championship?,what <DURATION> did <ORGANIZATION> win championship?,X,,,,,
what did coolidge believe with regards to the role of government?,what did <PERSON> believe with regards to the role of government?,X,,,,,
what is the atlanta braves mascot?,what is the <ORGANIZATION> mascot?,X,,,,,
what type of government did england have during the glorious revolution?,what type of government did <LOCATION> have during the glorious revolution?,X,,,,,
who played dumbledore in the first movie?,who played <PERSON> in the <ORDINAL> movie?,X,,,,,
where was greenpeace an international environmental organization founded?,where was <ORGANIZATION> an international environmental organization founded?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(n) where m.name=<ORGANIZATION> return n.name,,,,
what does roger that mean?,what does <PERSON> that mean?,X,,,,,
what is the center of london called?,what is the center of <LOCATION> called?,X,,,,,
what was the first name of the washington redskins?,what was the <ORDINAL> name of the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
what sports do they do in canada?,what sports do they do in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who was the first leader of the afl?,who was the <ORDINAL> leader of the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
who is the arizona cardinals football coach?,who is the <ORGANIZATION> football coach?,O,match (org)-[:HEAD_COACH]-(c) where org.name=<ORGANIZATION> return c.name,,,,
when did tamu admit women?,when did <LOCATION> admit women?,X,,,,,
where was the battle of waterloo held?,where was the battle of <LOCATION> held?,X,,,,,
what was marilyn monroe known for?,what was <PERSON> known for?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what has barack obama done wrong?,what has <PERSON> done wrong?,X,,,,,
which is faster amd dual core or intel dual core?,which is faster amd dual core or <ORGANIZATION> dual core?,X,,,,,
where did lee corso go to college?,where did <PERSON> go to college?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who are the colorado eagles?,who are the <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (h) where h.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.descEn,,,,
what time period did jesus live in?,what time period did <PERSON> live in?,X,,,,,
where does lala anthony live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
what currency do they accept in kenya?,what currency do they accept in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what river did henry hudson sail up?,what river did <PERSON> sail up?,X,,,,,
what currency is used in switzerland 2012?,what currency is used in <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what do they speak in iran?,what do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
who did ayrton senna drive for?,who did <PERSON> drive for?,X,,,,,
what happened to madonna childhood home?,what happened to <PERSON> childhood home?,X,,,,,
where is the best place to vacation in the dominican republic?,where is the best place to vacation in the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what made ancient rome fall?,what made ancient <LOCATION> fall?,X,,,,,
where was brad pitt born?,where was <PERSON> born?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
what position does vernon davis play?,what position does <PERSON> play?,O,match (h:Human)-[:POSITION_PLAYED_ON_TEAM]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
where is the euro 2012 tournament?,where is the <MISC> ?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION]-(loc) where m.name=<MISC> return loc.name,,,,
what time is right now in texas?,what time is <DATE> in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what to see and do in malta?,what to see and do in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where did dolly parton grew up?,where did <PERSON> grew up?,X,,,,,
what state is rick santorum from?,what state is <PERSON> from?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
what countries does queen elizabeth ii reign?,what countries does queen <PERSON> reign?,O,MATCH (x)-[:HEAD_OF_STATE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
when did the aurora colorado shooting take place?,when did the <LOCATION> shooting take place?,X,,,,,
what is jonas brothers names?,what is <PERSON> brothers names?,X,,,,,
what art movements was henri matisse involved in?,what art movements was <PERSON> involved in?,O,match (h)-[:MOVEMENT]-(m) where h.name=<PERSON> return m.name,,,,
what are some famous tourist attractions in germany?,what are some famous tourist attractions in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who's kobe bryant?,who's <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what type of government system does saudi arabia have?,what type of government system does <LOCATION> have?,X,,,,,
what countries did czechoslovakia become?,what countries did <LOCATION> become?,X,,,,,
what songs did richard marx write?,what songs did <PERSON> write?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what did ryan dunn died from?,what did <PERSON> died from?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what war was george washington associated with?,what war was <PERSON> associated with?,X,,,,,
where was zachary taylor elected from?,where was <PERSON> elected from?,X,,,,,
who does kris humphries play for in the nba?,who does <PERSON> play for in the nba?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where tupac grew up?,where <MISC> grew up?,X,,,,,
where did al capone go to jail?,where did <PERSON> go to jail?,X,,,,,
what type of music did richard wagner play?,what type of music did <PERSON> play?,O,match (h)-[:GENRE]-(g) where h.name=<PERSON> return g.name,,,,
what do you call money in brazil?,what do you call money in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what team did tim tebow play for in college?,what team did <PERSON> play for in college?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what airport in paris?,what airport in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what nationality was andy williams?,what nationality was <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where did matthew brady live?,where did <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
what ball does rickie fowler play?,what ball does <PERSON> play?,X,,,,,
who are the broncos players?,who are the <ORGANIZATION> players?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where do most of the people live in japan?,where do most of the people live in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
in what country do they speak basque?,in what country do they speak <MISC>?,O,match (h)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(lang) where lang.name=<MISC> return h.name,,,,
where is belgium at?,where is <LOCATION> at?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(p) where o.name=<LOCATION> return p.name,,,,
what religions are in russia?,what religions are in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what government system does north korea have?,what government system does <LOCATION> have?,O,match (n)-[:BASIC_FORM_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(m) where n.name=<LOCATION> return m.name,,,,
what did einstein do?,what did <PERSON> do?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:OCCUPATION]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
in what country is amsterdam?,in what country is <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:COUNTRY]-(c) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what are the most common religions in the united states?,what are the most common religions in the <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what did martin luther king jr go to college for?,what did <PERSON> go to college for?,X,,,,,
where did sir ernest shackleton come from?,where did <PERSON> come from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what made jimi hendrix great?,what made <PERSON> great?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who did aaron rodgers play college football 4?,who did <ORGANIZATION> football <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
who plays nathan scott?,who plays <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
when did the houston rockets win the championship?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> win the championship?,X,,,,,
where is mount whitney?,where is <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(p) where o.name=<LOCATION> return p.name,,,,
who created the character of romeo?,who created the character of <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what are some places to visit in new york?,what are some places to visit in <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(p) where p.name=<LOCATION> return o.name,,,,
what are the countries and capitals of central america?,what are the countries and capitals of <LOCATION>?,O,"match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> match (cap)-[:CAPITAL_OF]-(n) return c.name, cap.name",,,,
where is puntland somalia?,where is <LOCATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(p) where o.name=<LOCATION> return p.name,,,,
what animal is on the western australian flag?,what animal is on the <MISC> flag?,X,,,,,
where did drew stanton play in college?,where did <PERSON> play in college?,O,match (h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what is kareem abdul jabbar real name?,what is <PERSON> real name?,O,match (h:HUMAN) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.birthName,,,,
what countries fall in eastern europe?,what countries fall in <LOCATION>?,O,match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what are taylor swift's albums?,what are <PERSON>'s albums?,O,match (a)-[:PERFORMER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> and a:ALBUM return a.name,,,,
who is the prime minister of ethiopia now?,who is the prime minister of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
when was mary poppins made?,when was <MOVIE> made?,O,match (f) where f.name=<MOVIE> return f.publicationDate,,,,
what did king edward vi died from?,what did king <PERSON> died from?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what did robert boyle accomplish?,what did <PERSON> accomplish?,X,,,,,
who did johnny bench play for?,who did <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
who does the islamic worship?,who does the <MISC> worship?,X,,,,,
where is napoleon buried?,where is <PERSON> buried?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_BURIAL]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what language do people speak in iceland?,what language do people speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
who sang at the mtv movie awards 2011?,who sang at the <ORGANIZATION> movie awards <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where do houston aeros play?,where do <ORGANIZATION> play?,X,,,,,
what is the new york knicks starting lineup?,what is the <ORGANIZATION> starting lineup?,X,,,,,
what to see and do in galway ireland?,what to see and do in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what year did brandon roy get drafted?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> get drafted?,X,,,,,
what are the names of michael jackson children?,what are the names of <PERSON> children?,O,match (h)->[:CHILD]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what is pennsylvania's state flower called?,what is <LOCATION>'s state flower called?,X,,,,,
what book did niccolo machiavelli write?,what book did <PERSON> write?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
what religions are found in australia?,what religions are found in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what college did drew bledsoe?,what college did drew <PERSON>?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where is the mtv headquarters?,where is the <ORGANIZATION> headquarters?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
who does michael vick play for?,who does <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what is guatemala current system of government?,what is <LOCATION> <DATE> system of government?,X,,,,,
what is anderson silva trained in?,what is <PERSON> trained in?,X,,,,,
what caused the asian currency crisis?,what caused the <MISC> currency crisis?,X,,,,,
which countries does russia border?,which countries does <LOCATION> border?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what season did brooke burke won?,what season did <PERSON> won?,X,,,,,
what does pixar produce?,what does <ORGANIZATION> produce?,O,match (w)-[:PRODUCER]-(h) where h.name=<ORGANIZATION> return w.name,,,,
what did emily dickinson die of?,what did <PERSON> die of?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
who was king or queen after james i?,who was king or queen after <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
who played lois lane in superman 1?,who played <PERSON> in superman <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what was elie wiesel's father's name?,what was <PERSON>'s father's name?,O,match (h)-[:FATHER]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> return f.name,,,,
where is st vincent de paul buried?,where is <PERSON> buried?,O,match (h)-[:PLACE_OF_BURIAL]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name,,,,
what language do fiji people speak?,what language do <LOCATION> people speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what victoria beckham kids names?,what <PERSON> kids names?,O,match (h)->[:CHILD]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where is new york in the map?,where is <LOCATION> in the map?,O,match (c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locatorMapImage; match(c) where c.name=<LOCATION> return c.locationMap,,,,
where did france surrender ww2?,where did <LOCATION> surrender ww2?,X,,,,,
what did jimmy valvano die with?,what did <PERSON> die with?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what teams did charles barkley?,what teams did <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
when was bill clinton elected president?,when was <PERSON> elected president?,X,,,,,
where did giovanni pierluigi da palestrina live?,where did <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
when was the 2012 calgary stampede?,when was the <DATE> <LOCATION> stampede?,X,,,,,
when michael jordan got drafted?,when <PERSON> got drafted?,X,,,,,
what kind of money do the philippines use?,what kind of money do the <LOCATION> use?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
who played dorothy in the wizard of oz movie?,who played <PERSON> in the <MOVIE> movie?,X,,,,,
who does marion barber play 4?,who does <PERSON> play <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what college did james franco go to?,what college did <PERSON> go to?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
how many teams are there in the ncaa football?,how many teams are there in the <ORGANIZATION> football?,X,,,,,
who is garrett pretty little liars?,who is <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what type of currency should i take to mexico?,what type of currency should i take to <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) return currency.name,,,,
what did lucille ball die of?,what did <PERSON> die of?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what religion was john f kennedy?,what religion was <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:RELIGION]-(r) where h.name=<PERSON> return r.name,,,,
where was the earthquake in chile 2010?,where was the earthquake in <LOCATION> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what style of art does andy warhol do?,what style of art does <PERSON> do?,O,match (h)-[:GENRE]-(g) where h.name=<PERSON> return g.name,,,,
what movies did ron howard do?,what movies did <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what county is charlotte north carolina?,what county is <LOCATION>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(n) where m.name=<LOCATION>  return n.name,,,,
what type of government and economic system does the united states have?,what type of government and economic system does the <LOCATION> have?,X,,,,,
who is michelle obama?,who is <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
where did kate middleton go to prep school?,where did <PERSON> go to prep school?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
what type of government does nigeria have today?,what type of government does <LOCATION> have <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what did hans oersted discovered in 1819?,what did <PERSON> discovered in <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what is the very first harry potter book?,what is the very <ORDINAL> <PERSON> book?,X,,,,,
what kourtney kardashian name her daughter?,what <PERSON> name her daughter?,O,match (h)->[:CHILD]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
when did the lions last win a thanksgiving game?,when did the <ORGANIZATION> last win a <DATE> game?,X,,,,,
what kind of government does chile have today?,what kind of government does <LOCATION> have <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where did richard arkwright die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
who played luke skywalker in star wars episode 4?,who played <PERSON> in star wars episode <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what movies has taylor lautner?,what movies has <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:PRESENT_IN_WORK]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where does sam bradford play?,where does <PERSON> play?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
where did vietnam originate?,where did <LOCATION> originate?,O,match (m)-[:NAMED_AFTER]-(o) where m.name=<LOCATION> return o.name,,,,
what was the first newspaper called in australia?,what was the <ORDINAL> newspaper called in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
where was hackney 2012 held?,where was <MISC> held?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION]-(loc) where m.name=<MISC> return loc.name,,,,
where does the st louis rams play football?,where does the <ORGANIZATION> play football?,X,,,,,
what year did scottie pippen come into the nba?,what year did <PERSON> come into the nba?,X,,,,,
where are you if you re in zagreb?,where are you if you re in <LOCATION>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(n) where m.name=<LOCATION>  return n.name,,,,
which country has won the cricket world cup the most times?,which country has won the cricket <MISC> the most times?,X,,,,,
what city was selena gomez born in?,what city was <PERSON> born in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:PLACE_OF_BIRTH]-(p) where h.name=<PERSON> return p.name ,,,,
who does dominic monaghan play in lord of the rings?,who does <PERSON> play in lord of the rings?,X,,,,,
which country does south africa border 2 the north?,which country does <LOCATION> border <NUMBER> the north?,O,match (c)-[:SHARES_BORDER_WITH]-(n) where c.name=<LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
who sang for pink floyd?,who sang for <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (h)-[:PART_OF]-(g) match (h)-[:OCCUPATION]-(o) where g.name=<ORGANIZATION> and o.name='singer' return h.name ,,,,
who played john connor friend in terminator 2?,who played <PERSON> friend in terminator <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what is the current time in nigeria lagos?,what is the current time in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what shows did henry winkler produce?,what shows did <PERSON> produce?,O,match (m)-[:PRODUCER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> return m.name,,,,
what state was texaco gas founded?,what state was <ORGANIZATION> gas founded?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(n) where m.name=<ORGANIZATION> return n.name,,,,
what is the official language of china and 3 other dialects?,what is the official language of <LOCATION> and <NUMBER> other dialects?,O,"match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> match (c)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(ul) return ol.name, ul.name",,,,
who is the senator of connecticut 2010?,who is the senator of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
when was the last time the dallas cowboys went to the super bowl?,when was the last time the <ORGANIZATION> went to the super bowl?,X,,,,,
what episode does rukia fade away?,what episode does <PERSON> fade away?,X,,,,,
what is brazil time zone?,what is <LOCATION> time zone?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
who wrote john 3 16 in the bible?,who wrote <PERSON> <NUMBER> in the bible?,X,,,,,
what do people in the czech republic speak?,what do people in the <LOCATION> speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
where did bruno mars get his start?,where did <PERSON> get his start?,X,,,,,
who was tex beneke?,who was <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what are all the things thomas edison invented?,what are all the things <PERSON> invented?,X,,,,,
what does albania speak?,what does <LOCATION> speak?,O,match (h)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(lang) where h.name=<LOCATION> return lang.name,,,,
what is shakira's nationality?,what is <PERSON>'s nationality?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where did the sultan of the ottoman empire live?,where did the sultan of the <MISC> empire live?,X,,,,,
who is playing bilbo baggins?,who is playing <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what position did george washington serve in the constitutional convention?,what position did <PERSON> in the constitutional convention?,X,,,,,
where is the 2012 ncaa basketball tournament?,where is the <MISC>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION]-(loc) where m.name=<MISC> return loc.name,,,,
what episode did kate leave ncis?,what episode did <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
where are the seneca indians now?,where are the <MISC> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what did farrah dad do?,what did <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
where did matt barnes play?,where did <PERSON> play?,O,match (m)-[:PART_OF]-(n) where m.name = <PERSON> return n.name,,,,
where does the jordan river begin?,where does the <LOCATION> begin?,X,,,,,
what college did lil wayne graduated from?,what college did lil <PERSON> graduated from?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
where did rihanna come from?,where did <PERSON> come from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
who does kurt busch drive for now?,who does <PERSON> drive for <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what years did the knicks win the championship?,what <DURATION> did the <ORGANIZATION> win the championship?,X,,,,,
what is the time zone in uk now?,what is the time zone in <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what does dustin diamond do now?,what does <PERSON> do <DATE>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what state did thomas jefferson live in?,what state did <PERSON> live in?,X,,,,,
where are google headquarters located?,where are <ORGANIZATION> headquarters located?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
who is princess leia?,who is princess <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what was richard wright known for?,what was <PERSON> known for?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where is the nascar hall of fame?,where is the <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(n) where m.name=<LOCATION>  return n.name,,,,
what do australia call their money?,what do <LOCATION> call their money?,O,match (loc)-[:CURRENCY]-(currency) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return currency.name,,,,
what was the name of wright brothers plane?,what was the name of <ORGANIZATION> plane?,X,,,,,
where is located university of leeds?,where is located <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
who is gilbert gottfried snl?,who is <PERSON> snl?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what language do they denmark?,what language do they <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> return ol.name,,,,
what did martin luther do?,what did <PERSON> do?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what team did grover cleveland alexander play for?,what team did <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what was eli whitney nationality?,what was <PERSON> nationality?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what was christiaan barnard famous for?,what was <PERSON> famous for?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where was dwight d. eisenhower from?,where was <PERSON> from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where do audi come from?,where do <ORGANIZATION> come from?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(n) where m.name=<ORGANIZATION> return n.name,,,,
what team is chris paul on?,what team is <PERSON> on?,O,match (m)-[:PART_OF]-(n) where m.name = <PERSON> return n.name,,,,
what to do washington dc december?,what to do <LOCATION> dc <DATE>?,X,,,,,
what language is spoken in singapore?,what language is spoken in <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> return ol.name,,,,
who is sanjay gupta married to?,who is <PERSON> married to?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what do singapore speak?,what do <LOCATION> speak?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> return ol.name,,,,
what movies did luke perry play in?,what movies did <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
who wrote the book of st. john?,who wrote the book of <MISC>?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where w.name=<MISC> return m.name,,,,
who is kobe bryant dad?,who is <PERSON> dad?,O,match (m)-[:FATHER]-(n) where m.name=<PERSON> return n.name,,,,
what continent does israel belong to?,what continent does <LOCATION> belong to?,O,match (n)-[:CONTINENT]-(c) where n.name=<LOCATION> return c.name,,,,
what is the capital city of albania?,what is the capital city of <LOCATION>?,O,match (cap)-[:CAPITAL_OF]-(n) where n.name=<LOCATION> return cap.name,,,,
where is thomas jefferson's home?,where is <PERSON>'s home?,X,,,,,
what is wentworth miller in?,what is <PERSON> in?,X,,,,,
what is the capital of spain in 2010?,what is the capital of <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,O,match (cap)-[:CAPITAL_OF]-(n) where n.name=<LOCATION> return cap.name,,,,
who killed harvey milk?,who killed <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what was the title of the first book dr. seuss wrote?,what was the title of the <ORDINAL> book <PERSON> wrote?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who owns nissan car manufacturer?,who owns <ORGANIZATION> car manufacturer?,O,match (o)-[:OWNED_BY]-(h) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return h.name,,,,
where is the university of west alabama located?,where is the <ORGANIZATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
what did kenny everett die off?,what did <PERSON> die off?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what main language do they speak in brazil?,what main language do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> return ol.name,,,,
where does joey king live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
what happened to justin bieber 2012?,what happened to <PERSON> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
how many australian states and territories?,how many <LOCATION> states and territories?,O,match (m)-[:CONTAINS_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(t) where m.name=<LOCATION> return t.name,,,,
what was manchester united first name?,what was <ORGANIZATION> name?,X,,,,,
who is the governor of hawaii now?,who is the governor of <LOCATION> <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
when did herbert hoover become president?,when did <PERSON> become president?,X,,,,,
where did elvis presley started his career?,where did <PERSON> started his career?,X,,,,,
what happened vince mcmahon?,what happened <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what jobs did harriet tubman have?,what jobs did <PERSON> have?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:OCCUPATION]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where does unesco operate?,where does <ORGANIZATION> operate?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
what does canada grow for food?,what does <LOCATION> grow for food?,X,,,,,
where in the bible does it talk about david?,where in the bible does it talk about <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what does amanda seyfried play in?,what does <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
what language do people speak in iran?,what language do people speak in <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where c.name=<LOCATION> return ol.name,,,,
what is the jurisdiction of the us supreme court?,what is the jurisdiction of the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
what voice does hank azaria do on the simpsons?,what voice does <PERSON> do on the simpsons?,X,,,,,
who is the leader of japan?,who is the leader of <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
what time zone is the uk in right now?,what time zone is the <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,O,match (m)-[:LOCATED_IN_TIME_ZONE]-(n) where m.name = <LOCATION> return n.name,,,,
what instrument does bela fleck play?,what instrument does <PERSON> play?,O,match (h)-[:INSTRUMENT]-(i) where h.name=<PERSON> return i.name,,,,
what position does ray allen?,what position does <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what branch is made up of the house of representatives?,what branch is made up of the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
where did kurds originate from?,where did <MISC> originate from?,X,,,,,
where did chancellorsville battle take place?,where did <LOCATION> battle take place?,X,,,,,
what year was the cubs last world series?,what <DURATION> was the <ORGANIZATION> last world series?,X,,,,,
who is playing hawkeye in the avengers movie?,who is playing <LOCATION> in the avengers movie?,X,,,,,
what country speak english as native language?,what country speak <MISC> as native language?,O,match (c)-[:OFFICIAL_LANGUAGE]-(ol) where ol.name=<MISC> return c.name,,,,
who was king or queen after victoria?,who was king or queen after <PERSON>?,X,,,,,
what movie did rihanna play in?,what movie did <PERSON> play in?,O,match (h:Human)-[:FILMOGRAPHY]-(f) where h.name=<PERSON> match (f)-[:HAS_PART]-(m) return m.name,,,,
when was the last time the oakland raiders were in the super bowl?,when was the last time the <ORGANIZATION> were in the super bowl?,X,,,,,
what religion was mary todd lincoln?,what religion was <PERSON>?,O,match (h)-[:RELIGION]-(r) where h.name=<PERSON> return r.name,,,,
who is the house of representatives made up of?,who is the <ORGANIZATION> made up of?,X,,,,,
who all has jason kidd played for?,who all has <PERSON> played for?,X,,,,,
where is headquarters of verizon?,where is headquarters of <ORGANIZATION>?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
where is the country of cyprus located?,where is the country of <LOCATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<LOCATION> return location.name,,,,
who invented dell computer?,who invented <ORGANIZATION> computer?,X,,,,,
where did morgan freeman come from?,where did <PERSON> come from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where did bob barker grow up?,where did <PERSON> grow up?,X,,,,,
what are king charles spaniels?,what are king <PERSON>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
when was the chinese flag designed?,when was the <MISC> flag designed?,X,,,,,
where did boston terriers come from?,where did <ORGANIZATION> come from?,X,,,,,
what makes einstein smart?,what makes <PERSON> smart?,X,,,,,
who played juni in spy kids 4?,who played <PERSON> in spy kids <NUMBER>?,X,,,,,
what year did the new york mets start?,what year did the <ORGANIZATION> start?,O,match (o) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return o.inception,,,,
where did neil gaiman grow up?,where did <PERSON> grow up?,X,,,,,
what books did aristotle wrote?,what books did <PERSON> wrote?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where is eu headquarters located?,where is <LOCATION> headquarters located?,O,match (o)-[:HEADQUARTERS_LOCATION]-(loc) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return loc.name,,,,
who runs the cornelia marie now?,who runs the <PERSON> <DATE>?,X,,,,,
where did john muir die?,where did <PERSON> die?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:PLACE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where was selena gomez raised?,where was <PERSON> raised?,X,,,,,
what countries are in the andean region?,what countries are in the <MISC> region?,X,,,,,
who created english alphabet?,who created <MISC> alphabet?,X,,,,,
what airport do you fly into for destin?,what airport do you fly into for <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
who played violet's mother in charlie and the chocolate factory?,who played violet's mother in <PERSON> and the chocolate factory?,X,,,,,
what country was george washington from?,what country was <PERSON> from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what year did pete rose play?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> play?,X,,,,,
where does kyla ross live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,,,,,
when did allen iverson get drafted?,when did <PERSON> get drafted?,X,,,,,
what does jackson browne sing?,what does <PERSON> sing?,O,match (a)-[:PERFORMER]-(h) where h.name=<PERSON> and a:Song return a.name,,,,
who plays ferris bueller's best friend?,who plays <ORGANIZATION>'s best friend?,X,,,,,
what has anna kendrick been in?,what has <PERSON> been in?,X,,,,,
what are the major imports of the united states?,what are the major imports of the <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what are the team colors for the pittsburgh steelers?,what are the team colors for the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,,,,,
what is the current government system in france?,what is the <DATE> government system in <LOCATION>?,X,,,,,
what did roy rogers die of?,what did <PERSON> die of?,O,match (h)-[:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
what is calabria italy?,what is <LOCATION>?,O,match (h:Human) where h.name=<PERSON> return h.descEn,,,,
what did the new orleans hornets used to be?,what did the <ORGANIZATION> used to be?,X,,,,,
what are the major religions practiced in israel?,what are the major religions practiced in <LOCATION>?,O,match (loc)-[:OFFICIAL_RELIGION]-(r) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return r.name,,,,
what does jamaica manufacturer?,what does <LOCATION> manufacturer?,X,,,,,
what years did andrew jackson run for president?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> run for president?,X,,,,,
what 4 countries make up great britain?,what <NUMBER> countries make up <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:CONTAINS_ADMINISTRATIVE_TERRITORIAL_ENTITY]-(t) where c.name=<LOCATION> return t.name,,,,
where did madoff live in nyc?,where did <PERSON> live in nyc?,X,,,,,
how many languages are there in the philippines?,how many languages are there in the <LOCATION>?,O,match (c)-[:LANGUAGE_USED]-(ul) where c.name=<LOCATION> return count(ul),,,,
what song is monifah famous for?,what song is <PERSON> famous for?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
who did heinrich himmler marry?,who did <PERSON> marry?,O,match (h)-[:SPOUSE]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who carries sherwin williams paint?,who carries <PERSON> paint?,X,,,,,
who was josh groban in crazy stupid love?,who was <PERSON> in crazy stupid love?,X,,,,,
where is the columbia university located?,where is the <ORGANIZATION> located?,O,match (o)-[r:LOCATED_IN_THE_ADMINISTRATIVE_ENTITY]-(location) where o.name=<ORGANIZATION> return location.name,,,,
what team does kris humphries play for in 2011?,what team does <PERSON> play for in <DATE>?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what did the scientist thomson discover?,what did the scientist <PERSON> discover?,X,,,,,
where did john boehner come from?,where did <PERSON> come from?,O,match (h)-[:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(c) where h.name=<PERSON> return c.name,,,,
where did martin luther king junior go to college?,where did <PERSON> go to college?,O,match(h)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(s) where h.name=<PERSON> return s.name,,,,
who was carrie underwood in soul surfer?,who was <PERSON> in soul surfer?,X,,,,,
who plays lois griffin in family guy?,who plays <PERSON> in family guy?,X,,,,,
what did julian fellowes write?,what did <PERSON> write?,O,match (m)-[:COMPOSER]-(w) where m.name=<PERSON> return w.name,,,,
where does selena gomez live map?,where does <PERSON> live map?,X,,,,,
who does the islam worship?,who does the <MISC> worship?,X,,,,,
who was married to lance armstrong?,who was married to <PERSON>?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what is venus named for?,what is <PERSON> named for?,O,match (m)-[:NAMED_AFTER]-(o) where m.name=<LOCATION> return o.name,,,,
who did john fox coach for?,who did <PERSON> coach for?,X,head_coach,,,,
where are the nuclear plants in uk?,where are the nuclear plants in uk?,X,,,,,
what years have the dodgers won the world series?,what <DURATION> have the <ORGANIZATION> won the <MISC>?,X,,,,,
what did farrah have surgery for?,what did <PERSON> have surgery for?,X,,,,,
who was the leader of the soviet union in 1945?,who was the leader of the <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,O,match (loc)-[:HEAD_OF_GOVERNMENT]-(h) where loc.name=<LOCATION> return h.name,,,,
who does john beck play for?,who does <PERSON> play for?,O,match (h:Human)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(b) where h.name=<PERSON> return b.name,,,,
what god do catholics believe in?,what god do <MISC> believe in?,X,no use,,,,
what movies have kenya moore produced?,what movies have <PERSON> produced?,X,no use,,,,
where did robbie hummel go to high school?,where did <PERSON> go to high school?,O,MATCH (p)-[:EDUCATED_AT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what year did the cleveland indians go to the world series?,what <DURATION> did the <ORGANIZATION> go to the world series?,X,no data,,,,
who owns the cleveland browns?,who owns the <ORGANIZATION>?,O,MATCH (o)-[:OWNED_BY]-(x) WHERE o.name = <ORGANIZATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
what language do jewish speak?,what language do <MISC> speak?,O,MATCH (m)-[:NATIVE_LANGUAGE]-(x) WHERE m.name=<MISC> RETURN x.name,,,,
what legal system does germany use?,what legal system does <LOCATION> use?,X,no use,,,,
who does danneel harris play on one tree hill?,who does <PERSON> play on <MOVIE>?,X,no relation,,,,
what inspired michelangelo?,what inspired <PERSON>?,X,no relation,,,,
what battle did germany surrender in ww2?,what battle did <LOCATION> surrender in <MISC>?,X,no use,,,,
who was the colts coach in 2011?,who was the <ORGANIZATION> coach in <DATE>?,X,no use,,,,
what airport is closer to downtown houston?,what airport is closer to downtown <LOCATION>?,X,no use,,,,
where does liz mcclarnon live?,where does <PERSON> live?,X,no relation,,,,
what city is fc schalke 04 in?,what city is fc <ORGANIZATION> <NUMBER> in?,X,no use,,,,
what system of government is used in south korea?,what system of government is used in <LOCATION>?,X,no use,,,,
where did giovanni da verrazano come from?,where did <PERSON> come from?,O,citizenship,,,,
what airport is close to daytona beach florida?,what airport is close to <LOCATION>?,X,no use,,,,
what was omar epps first movie?,what was <PERSON> <ORDINAL> movie?,X,no use,,,,
who did the baltimore ravens draft in 2011?,who did the <ORGANIZATION> in <DATE>?,X,no data with date,,,,
who won the governor election in puerto rico?,who won the governor election in <LOCATION>?,X,no data,,,,
where did william shakespeare perform most of his plays?,where did <PERSON> perform most of his plays?,X,no data,,,,
what group is aubrey o'day in?,what group is <PERSON> in?,O,MATCH (p)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what college did joe namath go to?,what college did <PERSON> go to?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:EDUCATED_AT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> AND x:University OR x:UniversityCollege OR x:PublicUniversity RETURN x.name,,,,
what wild animals live in colorado?,what wild animals live in <LOCATION>?,X,no use,,,,
where is eu parliament?,where is <LOCATION> parliament?,X,no data,,,,
when does summer start in new england?,when does <DATE> start in <LOCATION>?,X,no data,,,,
who invented arabic alphabet?,who invented <MISC> alphabet?,X,no data,,,,
where was president lyndon johnson from?,where was <PERSON> from?,O,"MATCH (p)-[r:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(x) WHERE p.name=<PERSON> RETURN x.name
",,,,
what did wagner compose?,what did <PERSON> compose?,X,no relation,,,,
what language did jewish people speak?,what language did <MISC> people speak?,X,no relation,,,,
who does michael oher play for in 2009?,who does <PERSON> play for in <DATE>?,X,no use,,,,
what years did barry bonds play?,what <DURATION> did <PERSON> play?,X,no use,,,,
who played emma frost?,who played <PERSON>?,X,no use,,,,
what does the mayan calendar say about 2012?,what does the <MISC> calendar say <DATE>?,X,no data,,,,
what clubs has peter crouch played for?,what clubs has <PERSON> played for?,X,no use,,,,
who plays the brother in hannah montana?,who plays the brother in <LOCATION>?,X,no use,,,,
what team does lamar odom play for 2011?,what team does <PERSON> play for <DATE>?,X,no data,,,,
what highschool did tom brady go to?,what highschool did <PERSON> go to?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:EDUCATED_AT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
who owns skywest?,who owns <ORGANIZATION>?,O,MATCH (o)-[r:OWNED_BY]-(x) WHERE o.name = <ORGANIZATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
who did michael jordan marry?,who did <PERSON> marry?,O,MATCH p=(x)-[r:SPOUSE]-(p) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where is the syracuse university?,where is the <ORGANIZATION>?,X,no data,,,,
what has mario lopez been in?,what has <PERSON> been in?,X,no data,,,,
where do logan browning live?,where do <PERSON> live?,X,no data,,,,
when did mcdonalds officially open?,when did <ORGANIZATION> officially open?,X,no data,,,,
what team does terrell owens play for this year?,what team does <PERSON> play for <DATE>?,X,no data,,,,
what to do with kids in halifax?,what to do with kids in <LOCATION>?,X,no data,,,,
where is lake waynoka ohio?,where is <LOCATION>?,X,no data,,,,
who did jeremy lin sign with?,who did <PERSON> sign with?,X,no data,,,,
who will sponsor kevin harvick in 2011?,who will sponsor <PERSON> in <DATE>?,X,no data,,,,
where adidas originate?,where <ORGANIZATION> originate?,O,MATCH (o)-[r:LOCATION_OF_FORMATION]-(x) WHERE o.name=<ORGANIZATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
who played emperor palpatine?,who played emperor <PERSON>?,O,MATCH (o)-[r:PERFORMER]-(x) WHERE o.name=<ORGANIZATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
what is 2pm est in philippines?,what is <TIME> est in <LOCATION>?,X,no data,,,,
where are the pyramids of giza located?,where are the pyramids of <LOCATION> located?,X,no use,,,,
when does sally pearson race tonight?,when does <PERSON> race <DATE>?,X,no relation,,,,
who were demeter's brothers and sisters?,who were <ORGANIZATION>'s brothers and sisters?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:SIBLING]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what instrument was louis armstrong famous for?,what instrument was <PERSON> famous for?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:INSTRUMENT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what date did the san francisco giants win the world series?,what date did the <ORGANIZATION> win the world series?,X,no data,,,,
what province is canada's capital located in?,what province is <LOCATION>'s capital located in?,O,MATCH (x)-[r:CAPITAL_OF]-(c) WHERE c.name = <LOCATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
on which continent is the usa located?,on which continent is the <LOCATION> located?,O,MATCH (c)-[r:CONTINENT]-(x) WHERE c.name=<LOCATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
where is singapore on a world map?,where is <LOCATION> on a world map?,X,no data,,,,
what to see in london in june 2012?,what to see in <LOCATION> in <DATE>?,X,no relation,,,,
what is the main language of israel?,what is the main language of <LOCATION>?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:LANGUAGE_USED]-(x) WHERE p.name = <LOCATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
what college did kerry collins?,what college did <PERSON>?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:EDUCATED_AT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> AND x:University OR x:UniversityCollege OR x:PublicUniversity RETURN x.name,,,,
what did bob ross die of?,what did <PERSON> die of?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:CAUSE_OF_DEATH]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
who was king hussein?,who was <PERSON>?,O,MATCH x=(p)-[]-() WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x,광범위한 질문,,,
where did martin luther live in?,where did <PERSON> live in?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:COUNTRY_OF_CITIZENSHIP]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
where is made kia car?,where is made <MISC>?,X,no data,,,,
what are all the songs nicki minaj is in?,what are all the songs <PERSON> is in?,O,MATCH (x)-[]-(p) WHERE x:Song AND p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what groups was hitler involved in?,what groups was <PERSON> involved in?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:INSTANCE_OF]-(x) WHERE p.name=<PERSON> RETURN x.name UNION MATCH (p)-[:MEMBER_OF]-(x) WHERE p.name=<PERSON> RETURN x.name,,,,
what college did magic johnson go to?,what college did <PERSON> go to?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:EDUCATED_AT]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> AND x:University OR x:UniversityCollege OR x:PublicUniversity RETURN x.name,,,,
what kind of language do they speak in greece?,what kind of language do they speak in <LOCATION>?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:LANGUAGE_USED]-(x) WHERE p.name = <LOCATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
what to see in chicago downtown?,what to see in <LOCATION> downtown?,X,no data,,,,
what kind of money does the philippines use?,what kind of money does the <LOCATION> use?,O,MATCH (l)-[:CURRENCY]-(x) WHERE l.name = <LOCATION> RETURN x.name,,,,
what did george eastman make?,what did <PERSON> make?,O,MATCH (p)-[r:COMPOSER]-(x) WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x.name,?,,,
what movies has billy burke been in?,what movies has <PERSON> been in?,X,no relation,,,,
who was rudolf virchow?,who was <PERSON>?,O,MATCH x=(p)-[]-() WHERE p.name = <PERSON> RETURN x,,,,
who were ulysses s grant and robert e lee?,who were ulysses s grant and <PERSON>?,X,no use,,,,
what is the last movie brittany murphy made?,what is the last movie <PERSON> made?,X,no use,,,,
with which countries does south africa trade?,with which countries does <LOCATION> trade?,X,no use,,,,
